Beats is a drama, comedy, music film directed by Brian Welsh.
Summer 1994, Scotland.
Johnno and Spanner are best mates, but Johnno’s family are moving him to a new town
and a better life, leaving Spanner behind to face a precarious future.
In pursuit of adventure and escape they head out on one last night
to an illegal rave before parting ways indefinitely.
Spanner, played by Lorn Macdonald.
Alison, played by Laura Fraser.
Robert, played by Brian Ferguson.
D-Man, played by Ross Mann.
Laura, played by Gemma McElhinney.
Cat, played by Amy Manson.
Beats is a 2019 American coming-of-age-drama film directed by
Chris Robinson and written by Miles Orion Feldsott.
The film stars Anthony Anderson, Khalil Everage, Uzo Aduba, Emayatzy
Corinealdi, Paul Walter Hauser, Dave East, Ashley Jackson, Evan J.
Simpson, and Dreezy, and follows a reclusive, teenage music prodigy who
forms an unlikely friendship with a struggling producer.
United by their mutual love of hip-hop, they try to free each other from the
demons of their past and break into the city's music scene.
It was released onto Netflix on June 19, 2019, and received
generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of friendship, scotland, rave culture, 1990s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.